<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quotes on Infinite Walk</title>
    <link>https://infinitewalk.com/categories/quotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quotes on Infinite Walk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infinitewalk.com/categories/quotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed feelings, assertive actions!</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/mixed-feelings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/mixed-feelings/</guid>
      <description>It is a time of transition for we all, it&amp;rsquo;s always been. We all see transitions in different ways, we see time differently as well. The online Oxford Dictionary describes transition as the process or period of changing from one stage or condition to another and also describes change as the ability to make or become different. Wherever you are and whatever you&amp;rsquo;re doing, as you read it if you&amp;rsquo;re not in a comfort zone and with a passive posture about everything around you chances are that you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing some sort of change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Few of Marshall McLuhan Quotes That Made My Day</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/marshall-mcluhan-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/marshall-mcluhan-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Whenever my work struggles to inspire me I switch last few hours of my evening to read something funny or inspiring quotes from Goodreads/Medium. Today, my way back to New York, I started reading an article on Medium.
Now, there you go my favorite quotes of Marshall McLuhan.
 &amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for what you want, what you want becomes the sacrifice.&amp;rdquo; —Author Unknown.
&amp;ldquo;Every society honors its live conformists and its dead troublemakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Startup Quotes for Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/twenty-startup-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/twenty-startup-quotes/</guid>
      <description>No matter how positive you’re, there will be times when negativity will kick you down; in those situations I hope following 20 quotes helps you to standup again.
 &amp;ldquo;God grant us the serenity to accept to things we cannot change, courage to change the things we can, and wisdom to know the difference.&amp;rdquo; —Reinhold Niebuhr
&amp;ldquo;The greatest danger for most of us is not that our aim is too high and we miss it, but that it is too low and we reach it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>