<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Infinite Walk</title>
    <link>https://infinitewalk.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Infinite Walk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infinitewalk.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mixed feelings, assertive actions!</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/mixed-feelings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/mixed-feelings/</guid>
      <description>It is a time of transition for we all, it&amp;rsquo;s always been. We all see transitions in different ways, we see time differently as well. The online Oxford Dictionary describes transition as the process or period of changing from one stage or condition to another and also describes change as the ability to make or become different. Wherever you are and whatever you&amp;rsquo;re doing, as you read it if you&amp;rsquo;re not in a comfort zone and with a passive posture about everything around you chances are that you&amp;rsquo;re experiencing some sort of change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All or Nothing</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/all-or-nothing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/all-or-nothing/</guid>
      <description>I do agree with Elle. No matter how stubborn we are, sometimes the world won&amp;rsquo;t just wheel on our terms. We can&amp;rsquo;t always say, &amp;ldquo;its my way or highway&amp;rdquo;. Its not all or nothing all the time. There are times when we need to compromise.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Certainly</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/certainly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/certainly/</guid>
      <description>I love this line a lot. Because confidence has been something I used to struggle with. Once, a friend of mine once told me, my confidence is not that they will like me, my confidence is, I will be fine even if they don&amp;rsquo;t.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>For Tom Shaw S.S.J.E. (1945-2014)</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/tom-shaw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/tom-shaw/</guid>
      <description>As you might have realized, Mary Oliver and her poems has great impact on me. Especially this one from &amp;ldquo;Felicity&amp;rdquo; reminds me of the loss of a great fried who used to love me to space and beyond. I had called her weeks before she passed away and told her, &amp;ldquo;Meet me for Lunch in New York City, I have a good news for you&amp;rdquo;. The week I was about to meet her, I got the saddest news that she passed away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hurricane</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/hurricane/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/hurricane/</guid>
      <description>I would definitely say this, &amp;lsquo;Mary Oliver is one of my favorite contemporary poets&amp;rsquo;. She has a way of romanticizing with mother nature. She is an “indefatigable guide to the natural world”. Her poems make me feel humanity. This poem from her Pulitzer prize winning poetry book &amp;ldquo;A Thousand Mornings&amp;rdquo; shows how we should live like trees, by not letting external things affect us, the way trees go through so much of events with change in seasons and storms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If There is Something to Desire, there will be something to regret</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/desire-regret/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/desire-regret/</guid>
      <description>These lines are important to me. Most often or not, I find myself in a position where I say yes to things I shouldn&amp;rsquo;t. And I learnt the hard way that, when you&amp;rsquo;re saying &amp;ldquo;yes&amp;rdquo; to someone, make sure you&amp;rsquo;re not saying &amp;ldquo;no&amp;rdquo; to yourself.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In The Midst of Winter</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/midst-of-winter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/midst-of-winter/</guid>
      <description>This poem has been one of my favorite all along. This tells us that the outside negativity has lesser impact than what lays inside. We are stronger than our fears. Greater than our limits. There is a light inside us that keeps us awake in the moment of darkness.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journey Wisely</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/journey-wisely/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/journey-wisely/</guid>
      <description>My mentor &amp;amp; partner-in-crime Shree Pragada, one of best human beings to talk to about existence of this world, metaphysical literature, and the God, often tells me, &amp;ldquo;this world doesn&amp;rsquo;t need our help. we are here to serve a purpose. We have got this one life to realize that one purpose, and fulfill it. This world is perfect just the way it is.&amp;rdquo; It made me realize we are insignificant in this universe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poem of The One World</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/one-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/one-world/</guid>
      <description>One for all, all for one.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sing to Me</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/sing-to-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/sing-to-me/</guid>
      <description>Love is all we got.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storage</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/storage/</guid>
      <description>I think this single line has more gravity than the core of universe. Mary Oliver beautifully pens down how sometimes what we think as our limitation is our strongest source power.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/the-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/the-future/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, I think life is just this, and nothing else. There is no certainty, there is no pre-determined rules. Life doesn&amp;rsquo;t come with a operating manual. And all five lives from Albert Camus says it all.
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The God</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/the-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/the-god/</guid>
      <description>Well, there are two kinds of people in this world; those who believe God, and those who don&amp;rsquo;t. Strangely, I am neither of them. However, this prose makes me debate with myself; which group I would like to belongs to?
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Few of Marshall McLuhan Quotes That Made My Day</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/marshall-mcluhan-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/marshall-mcluhan-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Whenever my work struggles to inspire me I switch last few hours of my evening to read something funny or inspiring quotes from Goodreads/Medium. Today, my way back to New York, I started reading an article on Medium.
Now, there you go my favorite quotes of Marshall McLuhan.
 &amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for what you want, what you want becomes the sacrifice.&amp;rdquo; —Author Unknown.
&amp;ldquo;Every society honors its live conformists and its dead troublemakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Martian — Movie That Changed My Perspective towards Work and Life</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-martian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-martian/</guid>
      <description>What will you do if you were left on a deserted planet like Mars, without anyone knowing about your survival? With having a life support systems of only 31 days! Will you give up? Or you will get to work and find every way possible for your existence?
 &amp;ldquo;At some point, everything is going to go south on you. Everything is going to go south, and you gonna say, this is it; this is how I end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Success - 10 Tips for the Road Less Travelled</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-struggle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for what you want, what you want becomes the sacrifice.&amp;rdquo; —Author Unknown
  Go to college: College won’t teach you anything that is useful in life. However, it will help you find what you like and what you don’t. It will help you find your passion. Don&amp;rsquo;t Complain: If there is a problem try to solve it, if you can’t; find someone who can. Stay Positive: A positive attitude might not solve all the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Startup Quotes for Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/twenty-startup-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/twenty-startup-quotes/</guid>
      <description>No matter how positive you’re, there will be times when negativity will kick you down; in those situations I hope following 20 quotes helps you to standup again.
 &amp;ldquo;God grant us the serenity to accept to things we cannot change, courage to change the things we can, and wisdom to know the difference.&amp;rdquo; —Reinhold Niebuhr
&amp;ldquo;The greatest danger for most of us is not that our aim is too high and we miss it, but that it is too low and we reach it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Better Meetings</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/better-meetings/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/better-meetings/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;People who enjoy meetings should not be in charge of anything.&amp;rdquo; —Thomas Sowell
 I hate meetings. I hate meetings as much as I hate religious people. Well, research from Harvard Business School &amp;amp; London school of Economics shows;
Top executives spend upwards of 18 hours per week - third of their working week - in meetings. Estimated 25-50% of meeting time considered wasted Research shows the cost of Unnecessary meeting to Business in terms of wasted salary hours as $37 Billion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Struggle - You Can’t Skip Day Two</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-success/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;There is no talent here, this is hard work. This is an obsession. Talent doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist, we are all equals as human beings. You could be anyone if you put in the time. You will reach the top and that&amp;rsquo;s that. I&amp;rsquo;m not talented, I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed.&amp;rdquo; —Conor McGregor
 This week I am reading Rising Strong a book by Brené Brown. A book about Falling down, going through the misery, trying again, falling, learning and staying strong when everything seems to fall apart.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>11 People I Would Love to Hire For My Team</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/perfect-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/perfect-team/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Management, if practiced well, can be the noblest of occupations; no others offer as many way to help people find those opportunities.&amp;rdquo; —Clayton M. Christensen, Innovators Dilemma
 Leadership and Management are two most important part of todays business. And matter of fact both of the elements can be developed well with practice. However, its also important to have a great team to achieve anything in today&amp;rsquo;s business. Because you might win a match alone but to win the championship you would need a team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Business Lessons to Learn from from SUITS</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/business-lessons-from-suits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/business-lessons-from-suits/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I refuse to answer on the grounds that I don&amp;rsquo;t want to.&amp;rdquo; —Harvey Spector, fictional character from Suits
 Recently, few of my friends recommended a TV show named &amp;ldquo;SUITS&amp;rdquo; to watch; they even shared the entire four seasons. Taking benefits of free times in my traveling schedule I tried to watch a few, and it became so addictive that I had finished the whole 4 seasons in few weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Tips for Applying Lateral Thinking in Product Design</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/lateral-thinking-in-product-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/lateral-thinking-in-product-design/</guid>
      <description>Out of box thinking: take a problem, find its obvious solution and eliminate it. Now think of alternative solution.
 &amp;ldquo;In our ability to think about something differently lies the power to make it different.&amp;rdquo; —Marianne Williamson
 1. ALWAYS THINK OF 10 TIMES BETTER NOT 10% BETTER Lateral Thinking is using your creative and imaginative thinking to arrive at the best possible solution.
Most of companies the today create products without this and there are some best companies who create a product with lateral thinking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What a travesty of human life?</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/human-life/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/human-life/</guid>
      <description>What a travesty of human life? Do we really matter in this highly globalized world? Connected virtually but disconnected physically and morally? The question I am really asking what is the value of life common civilians like us? Are we really puppets in the hand of powerful hegemonic people or govt.
Let me explain my exasperation through few examples:
 Syria: We all know about this. But still I am putting a picture of this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save Your City Before It gets Ubered</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/uber-ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/uber-ed/</guid>
      <description>My Tribe — business travelers, the technophiles, the Internet enthusiasts, the the conference-speakers — are thrilled about Uber. Whenever I need to take a ride, I touch that icon on my iPhone — the one with the logo of a superhero, and within few minutes appears a car with a well civilized driver.
uber Uber — convenience of reaching anywhere.
Don’t get me wrong. For all the reasons I like Uber, for equally same reasons I love public transport as well (in few cities in India like Bangalore and Delhi).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Get Distracted by the City</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/distracted-by-the-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/distracted-by-the-city/</guid>
      <description>I met Israel Shaw in a BBQ party in New York City through a mutual friend of mine, Anthony. Hours into conversation he showed me one of his poems, &amp;lsquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Get Distracted by the City&amp;rsquo;. His poem got my attention, especially those two lines in which he writes insignificant of us in this vast universe: We fall in circles through a billion galaxies, hanging in a fragile orbit. Part of which connects to my previous post of Journey Wisely.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hate Feeds The Hate</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/hate-feeds-the-hate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/poetry/hate-feeds-the-hate/</guid>
      <description>This one spots to the division and non-symmetry we have in our society as this point. We need to remind ourselves that we are all one and we need to love each other. Have we forgotten the rules of our existence today?
Download this poem as image, text, or pdf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Follow Your Passion is So Overrated?</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/follow-your-passion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/follow-your-passion/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;My fault, my failure, is not in the passions I have, but in my lack of control of them.&amp;rdquo; —Warren Buffett
 There is a paraphrase exchanged between Alice and Cheshire Cat in Lewis Carroll’s Alice in Wonderland:
 “If you don’t know where you’re going, any road will take you there.”
 I have done nothing significant yet in business world, but I’ve learn something very important from my early career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiring Your Own Superstar</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/hiring-superstars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/hiring-superstars/</guid>
      <description>1. HIRE FOR ATTITUDE THAN APTITUDE  &amp;ldquo;In looking for someone to hire, you look for three qualities: integrity, intelligence, and energy. But the most important is integrity, because if they don&amp;rsquo;t have that, the other two qualities, intelligence and energy, are going to kill you.&amp;rdquo; —Warren Buffett
 I have always valued attitude of a person far much higher than her aptitude. Because you will and always can change a person&amp;rsquo;s aptitude but attitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rubens</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/rubens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 14:50:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/rubens/</guid>
      <description>Infinite Walk
with Rubens A blog to explore the adventures of life.
Name: Rubens Brotto
Dream: Connecting people and business for the greater good
Inspired by: Real people’s stories
Goto book: The Servant: A Simple Story About the True Essence of Leadership
Favorite quote: “I used to believe that leadership was about style but now I know that leadership is about substance, namely character.”
Best way to reach me: ask me anything on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Umakant</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2016 14:50:39 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Infinite Walk
with Umakant A blog to explore the adventures of life.
Name: Umakant Jani
Companies: Founder of Elysiais, and Lead Designer at Pivotis
Dream: Creating a platform which will allow everyone to have equal access to finance.
Technologies involved: AI, Machine Learning, Deep learning &amp;amp; Blockchain
Inspired by: Act of kindness and social change
Goto book: The Alchemist
Favorite quote: “It&amp;rsquo;s the courage to continue that counts”
Best way to reach me: ask me anything on Twitter</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>