<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on Infinite Walk</title>
    <link>https://infinitewalk.com/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on Infinite Walk</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://infinitewalk.com/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Few of Marshall McLuhan Quotes That Made My Day</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/marshall-mcluhan-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/marshall-mcluhan-quotes/</guid>
      <description>Whenever my work struggles to inspire me I switch last few hours of my evening to read something funny or inspiring quotes from Goodreads/Medium. Today, my way back to New York, I started reading an article on Medium.
Now, there you go my favorite quotes of Marshall McLuhan.
 &amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for what you want, what you want becomes the sacrifice.&amp;rdquo; —Author Unknown.
&amp;ldquo;Every society honors its live conformists and its dead troublemakers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Success - 10 Tips for the Road Less Travelled</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-struggle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/the-struggle/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t sacrifice for what you want, what you want becomes the sacrifice.&amp;rdquo; —Author Unknown
  Go to college: College won’t teach you anything that is useful in life. However, it will help you find what you like and what you don’t. It will help you find your passion. Don&amp;rsquo;t Complain: If there is a problem try to solve it, if you can’t; find someone who can. Stay Positive: A positive attitude might not solve all the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>20 Startup Quotes for Entrepreneurs</title>
      <link>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/twenty-startup-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://infinitewalk.com/posts/twenty-startup-quotes/</guid>
      <description>No matter how positive you’re, there will be times when negativity will kick you down; in those situations I hope following 20 quotes helps you to standup again.
 &amp;ldquo;God grant us the serenity to accept to things we cannot change, courage to change the things we can, and wisdom to know the difference.&amp;rdquo; —Reinhold Niebuhr
&amp;ldquo;The greatest danger for most of us is not that our aim is too high and we miss it, but that it is too low and we reach it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>